Killers Anonymous is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Martin Owen.
A failed attempt to murder a Senator is connected to a group meeting
secretly to discuss their darkest urges—to take lives.
Markus, played by Tommy Flanagan.
Jade, played by Jessica Alba.
The Man, played by Gary Oldman.
Alice, played by Rhyon Nicole Brown.
Joanna, played by MyAnna Buring.
Leandro, played by Michael Socha.
Killers Anonymous is a 2019 American crime thriller film, directed by Martin
Owen, from a screenplay by Owen, Elizabeth Morris and Seth Johnson.
It stars Tommy Flanagan, Rhyon Nicole Brown, Jessica Alba, Gary Oldman,
MyAnna Buring, Michael Socha, Tim McInnerny and Sam Hazeldine.
It was released on June 28, 2019, by Lionsgate.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.